MAULANA AHMAD MALIKI

PROFILE

I'm an undergraduate student from Brawijaya University. I've experience in Data Science and Software Developer. I'm self-driven and purposeful individual with critical thinking and passion in Software development. But other than that, I'm understand that still have a long way to go. So can maximize my potential in Software Developer, especially Data Science.

Education

Brawijaya University, Malang Bachelor's Degree Computer Science

(July 2018 - Present)

GPA: 3.22 / 4.00

SMK PGRI 3, Malang Vocational High School Software Engineering

(June 2015 - July 2018)

Experience

PT. Logee Trans, Jakarta Data Science

(July 2021 - November 2021)

As an intern, friendly and punctual in completing assignments. working in data analysis and data visualization.

- Perform analysis of company data for research development.
- Perform data visualization and analysis to increase visibility.
- Create algorithmic models to predict product delivery prices.

PT. Valsix Kreasi Teknologi, Surabaya software Developer

(June 2016 - July 2017)

As a student, the interns are friendly and punctual in completing assignments. working in website development.

- Development of appearance on a website.
- Checking the appearance of the website visibility.

"Kampung Budaya", Brawijaya University Deputy Head of Division Publication and Information

(April 2019 - January 2020)

Technology

Manage staff to be responsible for each task. Create and maintain a website system and provide information related to "Kampung Budaya".

- Creating a website display "Kampung Budaya".
- Checking the display on the visibility of the "Kampung Budaya" website.
- Development of the "Kampung Budaya" website.

PK2MABA FILKOM, Brawijaya University Staff Of Division Publication and Information Technology

(May 2019 - January 2020)

As the staff is friendly and responsible for every task. working in developing the "simaba-filkom" website.

- Make the appearance of the website "simaba-filkom".
- Checking the visibility of the "simaba-filkom" website.
- Development of the "simaba-filkom" website.

Projects

Fashion Product Image Classification

Classification of fashion product images by product Category.

Diabetes Classification

Diabetes classification using the knn algorithm, random forest, and adaboost.

Drug Classfication Based On Sentiment Analysis

NLP Sentiment analysis review based on uci machine learning repository dataset review.

Wind Power Prediction

Wind power prediction using the LSTM algorithm, dataset kaggle.com.

Certification

Managing Machine Learning Projects with Google Cloud,

Coursera

20 September 2020 Source: https://coursera.org/

Machine Learning, Dicoding

20 May 2022

Source: https://www.dicoding.com/

Basic Data Visualization, Dicoding

20 September 2020

Source: https://www.dicoding.com/

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SCSS, SASS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, Node JS, Reactjs, SQL, Firebase, MonggoDB, Python, Anaconda, Pandas, Numpy, Keras, Pytorch, Data Analysis, Data Visualization, Machine Laerning.